

# Ali Navidi **♀** Sari, Iran → +989339668289 2 years of experience ali\_navidi24@yahoo.com

westernal 🕠 ali-navidi-850a80209 in westernal 🔰

ali-navidi 🖹

Junior Front-End Developer

A highly motivated 4-year BSc. Computer Engineering student interested in frontend web developing with high team-working and punctuality ability eager to further knowledge and experience with professionals in the related field.

Skills: (Next.js JavaScript SEO Git Bootstrap Remix **c** ) React.js HTML CSS TypeScript Node.js Cypress Express.js MongoDB Svelte Java Tailwind GraphQL Python

# Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

Projects

#### social-media-frontend

Oben Origin co.

www.westernal.net/ github.com/westernal/social-media-frontend

Westernal: a full stack social media based on songs

JavaScript, CSS, Cypress, Next.js

#### social-media-backend

Westernal: a full stack social media

JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

#### Cinema

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Watching and downloading movies website and progressive web app (PWA) with Next.JS and TypeScript

TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

Sari-sartel: a mobile and accessories shop.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

#### Dashboard

Admin dashboard using Next JS

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

## Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

# **Publications**

# Introducing Westernal: A social media based on songs

**DEV Community** 

## dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9

#### How do you write your CSS?

**DEV Community** 

dev.to/westernal/how-do-you-write-your-css-3pg2

### Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced